Kheel, Theodore W. Additional Files. 6021/010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Financial Statements Analysis Worksheets (CNB-TV), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- CNB-TV Accounts Receivable, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- CNB - Accounts Receivable, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- CNB - Accounts Receivables, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Chandler, charlotte - Groucho Marx, 1977-1998 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Chatsworth, RE: Daniel Kampel Associates Correspondence, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Chatsworth, RE: Daniel Kampel Associates Financials, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Chatsworth, RE: Daniel Kampel Associates Brochures, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Chatsworth, RE: Prudential Correspondence, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Chatsworth, RE: Prudential CV, Dan Maclean, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Chatsworth, RE: Prudential Legal Research, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Chatsworth, RE: Prudential List of Unions, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Global Corporate Communications Chatsworth, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Chatsworth Capital Corp. - Global Corp. Communications West Peak + Reich+ Tang, inter Access, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- American Opp. Trust (Chatsworth) (Joel Matcovsky) RE: Reich + Tang, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- American Opp. Trust (Chatsworth) (Joel Matcovsky) RE: West Peak, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- children's television Workshop - correspondence + Memos, 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Christo Gates Project, Public Relations - Paul Wilmot correspondence, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Christo Gates Project, Public Relations - Paul Wilmot Agreement. Contract with Paul Wilmot, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Christo Gates Project, Public Relations - Paul Wilmot Overview, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Christo Gates Project, Public Relations - Paul Wilmot Press Releases, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Christo Gates Project, Public Relations - J. Walter Thompson correspondence, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Christo Gates Project, Public Relations - J. Walter Thompson Proposed Agreement with J. Walter Thompson, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Christo, The Gates RE: Gates Project (General), 1992-1998 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- (Christo/Jeanne-Claude) Promotional Materials - (A) Information on the Gates Pin Designed by Ellen Jacobs, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Consultants Proposals/Agreements Nurture New York's Nature, Inc., Omnicom Team/Fathom Communications, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Consultants Proposals/Agreements Presentation: Lange Marketing - commercial Development Preliminary Strategy implications, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Consultants Proposals/Agreement Presentation: Carbone Smolan Agency, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- consultants Proposals/Agreements Harbor Communications, The Gates Project, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Christo - Gates Project Presentation - Haruko Smith (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Christo Presentations - Gates Project Presentation Icon, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Presentations - Gates Project Proposal Presentation/Information to Consider (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Christo Gates - City Law - Newsletters, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- (Related Materials) Christo Gates RE: CPC Agreement (Central Park Conservancy) (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Writers guild of America/ Children's Television Workshop (CTW) - Proposal, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- WGA/CTW Freelance Agreement, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- WGA/CTW - Basic Agreement, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- WGA/CTW - Basic Agreement, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- CTW/AFTRA - Negotiations (miscellaneous), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- WGA/CTA - CTW 1st Proposal, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  Dec 12
- WGA/CTW - WGA 1st Proposal, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- WGA/CTW - WGA Proposal, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  Jan 9
- WGA/CTW - Fitts - Proposal, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  Feb 3
- WGA/CTW - CTW Proposal, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  Feb 13
- WGA/CTW - Other Unions, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- WGA/CTW - CTW Fringe Benefits (Box 17, Folder 11)
- WGA/CTW - Science Show Data, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- WGA/CTW - Form SS Writers Agreement (Sesame Sheet), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- WGA/CTW - WGA Agreement, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- WGA/CTW - Captain Kangaroo CBS, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- CTW / American Federation of Television + Radio Artists (AFTRA) - Industrial contract, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- CTW/AFTRA - Proposal, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- CTW/AFTRA - Financial Data, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- CTW/AFTRA - Meeting Notes, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- CTW/AFTRA - Basic Agreement, 1975-1978 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- CTW/AFTRA - Side Letter, 1975-1978 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- 1975-1978 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- CTW/AFTRA - side Letter, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  Jan 1
- CTW/AFTRA - Side Letter, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- CTW/AFTRA Side Letters, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- CTW/AFTRA - WNET Agreement, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- CTW/AFTRA - correspondence, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Christo Gates Project - Draft Agreements Agreement btwn Christo, Jeanne - Claude + CUJ + Central Park Conservancy, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Christo - Gates Project - Draft Agreement Agreement btwn City of NY/PKS + Recreation + Carriage House, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Corporate Documents - By Laws - Christo Gates Gates Public Private Partnership By-Laws, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Proposed Agreement btwn NYC Parks + Recreation + Gates Public Private Partnership, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Agreement - Central Park conservancy (CPC) w/ the City of New York Parks + Recreations Christo-Gates, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Sample Parks Agreements (Sting and Cow Parade) (Christo-Gates), 2002 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Presentation Museum of National history (Christo-Gates), 2004 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- American Museum of Natural history Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- MOMA Online Store correspondence (Museum of Modern Art) Christo Gates, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Website and Products - Metropolitan Museum of art, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- News release - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Wurth Collection October 12 Event at the National Academy of Design, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Draft Agreements/Christo Wurth collection, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- The Gap/Alexandra Files, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Agreement w/ Annemark Schoefer - Marketing Prints, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  May 28
- Agreement btwn Dillon/Thompson + Nurture New York's Nature, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Art Prints (Drawings for the Gates), 2003 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Christo-Gates - Nurture New York's Nature Projects, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Christo-gates - Nurture New York's Nature + Verizon, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Presentation Verizon - Christo-Gates, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Verizon Presentation 2 (Christo-gates), 2004 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Verizon Presentation 3 - Christo Gates - Nurture NYS Nature, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  June 23
- Christo-Gates - Project Application, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- IRS Information Financial, 2000-2002 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Correspondence Christo-Gates RE: New York Line of Credit with 10 Arts Patrons (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Christo/Jeanne - Claude General Correspondence, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Christo/Jeanne - Claude General correspondence, 1981-2002 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Notes/Frequently Questions - Christo Gates, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Description of the Gates, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Christo/Jeanna Claude Press Releases, 2003-2005 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Articles Christo Gates, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- the Gates - Christo/Jeanne Claude Articles - Extra copies, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- ECF Reporter Winter Article, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Fall 2004 "Blackbook" Magazine - Article on Christo (Box 19, Folder 9)
- budget Living Magazine - Ad, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  April/may
- august/September Budget Living Magazine -ad, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Article + Ads Dan's Papers, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  Oct 31
- Christo-gates Project - Articles and Ads The Nation Article, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  March 28
- Christo - Gates Project - articles and Ads the New York Daily News Online, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Christo-Gates Project - Articles and Ads The New York Daily News online, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  Feb 8
- Christo - Gates Project - Articles and Ads The New York Daily News Online, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  Feb 7
- Christo - gates Project - Articles and Ads New York Post, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Christo-gates New York Post Article, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  April 30
- The New York sun, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  Oct 30
- Christo-Gates Project - Articles + Ads The New York Times - Article, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  June 9
- Christo-Gates Project - Articles and Ads The New York times, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  Feb 27
- Christo-Gates Project - Articles and Ads The New York times, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  Feb 17
- Christo - gates Project - Articles and Ads The New York Times, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  Feb 16
- Christo - Gates Project - articles and Ads The New York Times, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Christo - Gates Project - Articles and Ads The New York Times, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  Feb 11
- Christo - Gates Project - Articles and Ads The New York Times, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  Feb 10
- Christo - Gates Project - Articles and Ads The New York Times, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Christo - Gates Project - Articles and Ads The New York Times, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Christo - Gates Project - Articles and Ads The New York Times Online, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Christo - Gates Project - Articles and Ads The New York Times, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  Feb 5
- Christo - Gates Project - Articles and Ads The New York Times, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  Jan 27
- Articles + Ads - NY Times Christo, "Gates: Arriving in Central Park", 2004 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  Nov 23
- Christo - Gates Project - Articles and Ads The New York Times Article, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  April 9
- New York Times Article - Christo - Gates, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  June 27
- New York Times Article Christo-Gates, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  June 6
- Christo-gates New York Times Article, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  May 18
- Christo-Gates New York times Article, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  Jan 23
- Christo-Gates New York Times Article, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  Dec 24
- Christo-Gates New York times Article, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 39)
- Christo-Gates New York times, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  July 3
- Christo-Gates New York times Article, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 41)
- Christo-Gates New York times Article, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 42)
- Christo-gates Project - Articles and Ads New York (Magazine), 2005 (Box 19, Folder 43)
- Christo-Gates Project - Articles and Ads The New Yorker, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  Jan 24 + 31
- Christo - Gates Project - Articles and Ads The New Yorker, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  March 29
- Christo-Gates Project - Articles and Ads thetimesledger.com - Article, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 46)
- Articles + Ads (Christo-Gates) Paul Hastings "Pro bono News" Articles, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  Winter
- Christo-Gates Project - Articles and Ads New York Law Journal, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  Feb 15
- Christo-Gates Project - articles and Ads City Law Publication, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  March/April
- Christo-Gates Project - Articles and Ads Northwest Indiana News: nwitimes.com, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  Feb 22
- Christo-gates Project - Articles + Ads Indiana Post-Tribune, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  Feb 20
- Christo-Gates Project - Articles and Ads WNBC.com, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 52)
- Christo-Gates Project - Articles and Ads WNET Thirteen Periodical, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  Feb
- The Wall Street Journal Article, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 54)
- The Wall St. Journal Article, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  Jan 13
- The Wall Street Journal Article, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 56)
- Christo-Gates - Articles + Ads - Worth (Robb Report), 2004 (Box 19, Folder 57)
- Parks + Trails New York Fall Gala to Honor Christo + Jeanne - Claude, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  Nov 28
- The Gates - Christo/Jeanne Claude Brochures + Maps, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 59)
- "Gates" Maps Accounted for, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 60)
- Art Installation Agreements, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 61)
- "Gates" Merchandise, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 62)
- Trade Mark Matters (Merchandise) Christo-Gates, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 63)
- Christo + Jeanne-Claude Watches Letter of intent, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 64)
- Website Information www.christojeanclaude.net, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 65)
- Christo - Jeanne Claude "Wrapped Reichstag" Berlin, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 66)
- CAE Investment Company, LLC, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Combustion Equipment Associates, Inc., 1978 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Collective Bargaining Luncheon Club, 1971-1976 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Columbia/Teachers' College Lerine, Arthur, 1997-1999 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- combustion Equipment Associates Inc. - Labor Matters Correspondence, 1971-1979 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Combustion Equipment Associates Inc. - Labor Matters Miscellaneous, 1964-1974 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Communications Satellite Corporation (COMSAT), 1971-1977 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Computer-generated Solutions (Phil Friedman) correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Computer Generated Solutions (Phil Friedman) Acadia business Plan, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Computer - Generated Solutions (Phil Friedman) Agreement with Task, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- computer - Generated Solutions (Phil Friedman) PERC Master Services Agreement, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Computer - Generated Solutions (Phil Friedman) Corporate Overview, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Computer - Generated Solutions (Phil Friedman) Strategic Alliance Agreement (Between CGS, Homework911.com + workforce distance learning (WDL)), 2000 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Computer - Generated Solutions (Phil Friedman) Invoices, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Correspondence (Cornell) - File List 2000 (Kheel Archive Papers) (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Cornell: RE: Gift of Segal Sculpture to Cornell, Pledges + Other Gifts (Box 20, Folder 16)
  Kheel Archive Papers
- Cornell - CALS Distance Learning Program, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Cornell - Ron Ehrenberg, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Cornell RE: Eric Ehrenberg, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Cornell: RE: Vermont Property - Gift to Cornell, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Cornell College of Architecture, Art + Planning 65 Becker St., 1997 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- CPR Institute for Dispute Resolution Correspondence/Letters of suspect, 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- CPR Institute for Dispute Resolution Prospectus, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- CPR Institute for Dispute Resolution Roster of Member Law Firms, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- CPR Institute for Dispute Resolution Global Program, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- CPR Institute for Dispute Resolution The Doris Dillon Center (Box 20, Folder 26)
- CPR Institute for Dispute Resolution - Alternatives Newsletter, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  March
- CPR Institute for Dispute Resolution - ADR Clauses + Procedures on Diskette (Box 20, Folder 28)
- CPR Institute for Dispute Resolution - Judge's Deskbook on Court ADR, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- ADR Procedures + Practice tools (CRP MAPP Services Vol. I), 1998 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- ADR in Industries + Practice Areas (CRP MAPP Series Vol. II), 1998 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- ADR in Industries + Practice Areas (CRP MAPP Series Vol. II), 1998 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Earth Times Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Earth times Certificate of Incorporation, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Earth times Johannesburg Summit, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Earth times Form Letter re: Fundacion Cristobal Gabarron, nd. (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Earth times Articles, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Earth Times Sublease Agreement, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Earth Times Invoices, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Earth Times Trade Out Agreement, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Earth times Pranay Gupte, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- The Earth Times (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Earth Times Monthly (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Clippings - Index (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Clippings - Affinity Group Credit Cards (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Clippings - Amer. Found on Automation + Employment, 1962-1967 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Clippings - Amer. Found on Automation + Empl., 1968-1973 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Clippings - Amer. Labor Movement, 1951-1969 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Clippings - American Labor Movement, 1970-1989 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Clippings - Arbitrations - AAU - NCAA (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Clippings - Arbitrations - Brewery Industry (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Clippings - Arbitrations - civil rights (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Clippings - Arbitrations - Entertainment Industry (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Clippings - Arbitrations - Maintime (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Clippings - Arbitrations - Milk Industry (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Clippings - Arbitrations - Newspaper + Printing Industries (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Clippings - Arbitrations - Pocketbook Workers Union - Leather Goods (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Clippings - Arbitrations - Rubber industry (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Clippings - Arbitrations - Teamsters (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Clippings - Arbitrations - Transit, 1953-1956 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Clippings - Arbitrations - Transit, 1957-1963 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Clippings - Arbitrations - Transit, 1965-1984 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Clippings - Automation (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Clippings - automation House, 1967-1970 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Clippings - Automation House, 1971-1976 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Clippings - center for Non-Broadcast Television (Automation House) (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Clippings - Christos Gates Project (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Clippings - civil Rights - Kheel Articles, Speeches (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Clippings - civil rights - Kheel Booklet + Book on EEO (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Clippings - civil Rights - NY + National Urban Leagues, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Clippings - civil Rights - National Urban League EEO Dive Civil rights Bill, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Clippings - civil rights national Urban League (Ghana, Airlines), 1957 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Clippings - civil rights - Natl. Urban League, 1958-1959 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Clippings - civil Rights - National Urban League, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Clippings - Civil Rights - Electrical Workers Union, 1962-1964 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Clippings - Civil Rights - Ghandi Society, 1962-1964 (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Clippings - Civil Rights - Alabama Libel Suits; Sullivan vs. NYT (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Clippings - civil Rights - President's committee on Equal Employment - Kheel Report, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Clippings - Civil Rights - Mayor's Comm. On Job Advancement (Box 22, Folder 36)
- Clippings - Civil Rights Local 6 Intl. Typographical Union Apprenticeship Plan (Box 22, Folder 37)
- clippings - civil Rights, 1968-1970 (Box 22, Folder 38)
- Clippings - Civil Rights - Minority Hiring City of NY, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 39)
- clippings - Columbia Univ: Campus Demonstration (Box 22, Folder 40)
- Clippings - Composes + Linguists Guild v. Television + Movie Producers (Box 22, Folder 41)
- Clippings - conflict Resolution General (Box 22, Folder 42)
- Clippings - conflict Resolution - Attica (Box 22, Folder 43)
- Clippings - conflict Res. - Bd of Mediation of community Disputes (Box 22, Folder 44)
- Clippings - Institute Center for Mediation + Conflict Resolution (Box 22, Folder 45)
- clippings - Electrical Industry (Box 22, Folder 46)
- clippings - Clay Felker - NY Mag. + Village Voice (Box 22, Folder 47)
- clippings - Foundation on employee Health, Medical Care + Welfare (Box 22, Folder 48)
- Clippings - David Graiver (Box 22, Folder 49)
- Clippings - Hospital - Strikes (Box 22, Folder 50)
- Clippings - industrial + Labor Relations - Air Transport (Box 22, Folder 51)
- Clippings - Industrial + Labor Relations + Alternatives to Strike (Monthly Labor Rev, Sept.), 1963 (Box 22, Folder 52)
- Clippings - Industrials + Labor Relations - Arbitration (Box 22, Folder 53)
- clippings - Industrial + Labor Relations - Shelling's Essay on Bargaining (Box 22, Folder 54)
- Clippings - Industrial + Labor Relations - Collective Bargaining, 1946-1963 (Box 22, Folder 55)
- Clippings - Industrials + Labor relations - collective Bargaining, 1964-1967 (Box 22, Folder 56)
- Clippings - Industrial + Labor Relations - collective Bargaining, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 57)
- Clippings - Industrial + Labor Relations - collective Bargaining, 1970-1980 (Box 22, Folder 58)
- Clippings - Industrial + Labor Relations - Mediation (Box 22, Folder 59)
- Clippings - Industrial + Labor Relations Public Sector Bargaining, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 60)
- Clippings - Experiments in Art + Technology (Box 22, Folder 61)
- Clippings - Industrial + Labor Relations, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 62)
- Clippings - Industrial + Labor Relations - Public Sector Bargaining, 1971-1973 (Box 22, Folder 63)
- Clippings - Industrial + Labor Relations - Studies (Box 22, Folder 64)
- Clippings - Industrial + Labor Relations - Taylor Law (Kheel Ppt. to speaker Travia) (Box 22, Folder 65)
- Clippings - Institute for Collective Bargaining + Group Relations, 1967-1969 (Box 22, Folder 66)
- Clippings - Institute for CellectiveBargaining + Group Relations, 1970-1987 (Box 22, Folder 67)
- Clippings - Kheel Awards, Honors + Special Recognition, 1948-1965 (Box 22, Folder 68)
- Clippings - Kheel - awards, Honors, Special recognition, 1966-1991 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Kheel - Biographical Materials, 1943-1958 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Kheel - Biographical Materials, 1959-1967 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Kheel - biographical materials, 1968-1970 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Kheel - Biographical materials, 1971-1979 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Kheel - biographical materials, 1980-1993 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Kheel - Corporate Directorships, Offices + Investments, 1955-1984 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Kheel - Favorable Media + Official comment, 1947-1963 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Kheel - Gilbane Housing Development in Panama, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Kheel - Litigation on Counsel, 1949-1993 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Kheel - Litigation as Party, 1969-1992 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Kheel's Relations of media, 1966-1994 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- John V. Lindsay as Mayor, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Local 6, International Typographical Union, 1965-1975 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- MARC (Metropolitan applied Research Center), 1967-1975 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- MGM Proxy Fight, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Maritimes Industry, 1957-1959 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Maritimes Industry, 1962-1963 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  July 2, 1962 - July 13, 1963
- Maritime Industry, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  Aug 10 - Oct 26
- Maritime Industry, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  Nov 2, 1963 - June 20, 1964
- Maritime Industry, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  Aug 3 - Dec. 23
- Maritime Industry, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Maritime Industry, 1966-1973 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Milk Driver Disputes + Strike, 1961-1974 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Municipal Government service (non-Transit), 1946-1947 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Municipal government service (non-Transit), 1948 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  Jan-Jun
- Municipal Government Service (Non-Transit), 1948 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  July 1 - Oct 26
- Municipal Government Service (Non-Transit), 1948 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  Nov 1-15
- Municipal Government Service (Non-Transit), 1948 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  Nov 16 -Dec 27
- Municipal govt. Service - Report of Mayor's Transit advisory committee, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  Sept. 9
- Municipal Government Service (Transit), 1946-1947 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Municipal Govt. service (Transit), 1948 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  Jan - June
- Municipal Government Service (Transit), 1948 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  July - Dec
- National Football League, 1968-1973 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- National Football League, 1974-1982 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- NY City + State Politics, 1946-1967 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- NY City + State Politics, 1968-1978 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- NY City + State Politics - gubernatorial (Cuomo v. Koch), 1982 (Box 23, Folder 38)
- NY City + State Politics Mayoral (Kheel v. Koch), 1981-1989 (Box 23, Folder 39)
- NYC Development + Economic Data, 1947-1965 (Box 23, Folder 40)